# JAMES VANSTEENKISTE

Software Developer at Race Roster



#### CONTACT

james@jamesvan.ca http://jamesvan.ca

### **SKILLS**

React, Vue.js & Svelte Typescript PHP Docker Kubernetes SQL

#### **EDUCATION**

# STUDIED COMPUTER SCIENCE

2013 - 2017

University of Western Ontario

# **ADDRESS**

500 Ridout St N London, ON N6A 0A2

# LANGUAGES

English

#### **SUMMARY**

From a young age, my parents knew I would have a future with technology. This idea probably formed from their many groundings given from finding me past curfew on the computer. Now in industry, this passion remains. I constantly push myself to understand new technologies to deliver the best experiences possible. There is certainly a mountain more to learn, and more problems to solve; knowing this is what keeps me enthusiastic and drives me everyday.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### ASICS RUNNING APPS - SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

From Match 2020

Full-Time

Full-stack developer pushing the legacy code base into more modern technologies and design patterns.

#### RADIANTS.GG - COFOUNDER

From June 2020

Building an A.I driven platform that delves deeper into the esport data to provide analysis and insight to players to help increase their rank, adapt to the latest meta changes, improve team composition.

#### SPORT-TRAVEL - LEAD SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

From May 2017 - March 2020

Full-Time

I led the software department at Sport-Travel where I pushed the team to develop scalable lightweight, progressive web applications. I approached leadership by encouraging idea sharing and regular employee participation. While also trying to lead by going above and beyond.

Our stack was build on Vue.js, Node.js deployed with CircleCI to Kubernetes on Google Cloud. Our data was stored relationally in MySQL with additional request caching and idempotency keys managed by Redis.

#### DUKETOYCO - CONTRACT WEB DEVELOPER

From Aug 2015 - July 2016

Part-Time

Web developer for DukeToyCo. Website design, online marketing, social media presence, and online branding.